(function(e){function t(t){for(var s,i,a=t[0],l=t[1],c=t[2],w=0,x=[];w<a.length;w++)i=a[w],Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(n,i)&&n[i]&&x.push(n[i][0]),n[i]=0;for(s in l)Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(l,s)&&(e[s]=l[s]);u&&u(t);while(x.length)x.shift()();return o.push.apply(o,c||[]),r()}function r(){for(var e,t=0;t<o.length;t++){for(var r=o[t],s=!0,a=1;a<r.length;a++){var l=r[a];0!==n[l]&&(s=!1)}s&&(o.splice(t--,1),e=i(i.s=r[0]))}return e}var s={},n={app:0},o=[];function i(t){if(s[t])return s[t].exports;var r=s[t]={i:t,l:!1,exports:{}};return e[t].call(r.exports,r,r.exports,i),r.l=!0,r.exports}i.m=e,i.c=s,i.d=function(e,t,r){i.o(e,t)||Object.defineProperty(e,t,{enumerable:!0,get:r})},i.r=function(e){"undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})},i.t=function(e,t){if(1&t&&(e=i(e)),8&t)return e;if(4&t&&"object"===typeof e&&e&&e.__esModule)return e;var r=Object.create(null);if(i.r(r),Object.defineProperty(r,"default",{enumerable:!0,value:e}),2&t&&"string"!=typeof e)for(var s in e)i.d(r,s,function(t){return e[t]}.bind(null,s));return r},i.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return i.d(t,"a",t),t},i.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)},i.p="/";var a=window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[],l=a.push.bind(a);a.push=t,a=a.slice();for(var c=0;c<a.length;c++)t(a[c]);var u=l;o.push([0,"chunk-vendors"]),r()})({0:function(e,t,r){e.exports=r("56d7")},"0050":function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":121,"title":"Genetic Algorithms: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Genetic Algorithms are based on which of the following?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"mutations","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Selection","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"both a and b","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Crossover allows us to combine two solutions together to obtain a new valid solution","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Valid solutions to genetic algorithm can be represented as _____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"genes","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"neurons","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"cells","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":221,"title":"Genetic Algorithms: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Genetic Algorithms can solve which of these tasks","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Schedule optimization","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Optimal packing","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"both of a and b","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"In implementing a genetic algorithm the first step is to randomly select two genes","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"When using Crossover operation the algorithm randomly selects _____ genes","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}]')},"034f":function(e,t,r){"use strict";r("85ec")},"221e":function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":103,"title":"Introduction to Neural Networks - Perceptron: Pre-Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Early neural networks required","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"manual weight adjusting","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"terabytes of data","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"special reasoning","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"A simple neuron is also called a \'threshold logic unit\'","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"A perceptron is a ___ type of model","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"multi-class classification","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"clustering","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"binary classification","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"id":203,"title":"Introduction to Neural Networks - Perceptron: Post-Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"To train a perceptron, find a weights vector that results in the smallest ___.","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"size","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"error","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"nodes","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"To minimize the function of weights, you can use gradient descent","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"During gradient descent, each step updates the ___","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"learning rate","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"weights","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"gradient","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},"229a":function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":118,"title":"Transformers: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Attention mechanism provides a means of _____ the impact of an inout vector on an output prediction of RNN","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"weighting","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"training","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"testing","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"BERT is an acronym for","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Bidirectional Encoded Representations From Transformers","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bidirectional Encoder Representations From Transformers","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Bidirectional Encoder Representatives of Transformers","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"In positional encoding the relative position of the token is represented by number of steps","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":218,"title":"Transformers: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Positional embedding _____ the original token and its position within the sequence","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"separates","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"compares","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"embeds","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Multi-Head Attention is used in transformers to give network the power to capture _____ of dependencies","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"different types","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"same type","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"none","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"In transformers attention is used in _____ instances","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},4757:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"IA para principiantes: Quizzes","complete":"¡Felicitaciones, has completado el cuestionario!","error":"Perdón, intente de nuevo","quizzes":[{"id":1,"title":"Introducción a la IA - Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"A famous 19th century proto-computer engineer was","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Charles Barkley","isCorrect":"false"},{"answerText":"Charles Babbage","isCorrect":"true"},{"answerText":"Charles Darwin","isCorrect":"false"}]},{"questionText":"Weak AI is a system designed to solve many tasks","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":"false"},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":"true"}]},{"questionText":"Chat bots are an example of truly intelligent systems","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"false, they are usually designed by a series of rules.","isCorrect":"false"},{"answerText":"true, they are usually considered to be \'intelligent\'.","isCorrect":"false"},{"answerText":"false, but they are increasingly able to pass Turing tests as they become more sophisticated.","isCorrect":"true"}]}]},{"id":2,"title":"Introducción a la IA: Post-Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"A top-down approach to AI is a model of reasoning called","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"strategic reasoning","isCorrect":"false"},{"answerText":"symbolic reasoning","isCorrect":"true"},{"answerText":"synergistic reasoning","isCorrect":"false"}]},{"questionText":"A bottom-up approach to AI might leverage a neural network to","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":"true"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":"false"}]},{"questionText":"The AI Winter occurred in this era","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"1950s","isCorrect":"false"},{"answerText":"1960s","isCorrect":"false"},{"answerText":"1970s","isCorrect":"true"}]}]}]}]')},"51b3":function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":122,"title":"Reinforcement Learning: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"To train RL model, we need","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Simulation environment","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Labeled dataset","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Unlabeled dataset","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is a good example of Reinforcement learning:","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Zero-shot image classification","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Zero-shot text classification","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Learning to play chess","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"When creating RL-based chess engine, we need to","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"use all existing chess matches as a dataset","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"let computer play against itself many times","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"program exhaustive search algorithm","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":222,"title":"Reinforcement Learning: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"How does RL training algorithm knows how well it did?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"It achieves high accuracy","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Using perplexity metric","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Using reward function","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Which problem(s) is RL is applicable to?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"With discrete environment","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"With continuous environment","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Both","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"In Actor-Critic model, critic predicts","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Reward function","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Best next action","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Probability of next actions","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},"56d7":function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r("2b0e"),n=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,r=e._self._c||t;return r("div",[r("nav",[r("ul",[r("li",[r("router-link",{staticClass:"navlink",attrs:{to:"/"}},[e._v("Home")])],1),e._m(0),r("li",[r("select",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.locale,expression:"locale"}],on:{change:function(t){var r=Array.prototype.filter.call(t.target.options,(function(e){return e.selected})).map((function(e){var t="_value"in e?e._value:e.value;return t}));e.locale=t.target.multiple?r:r[0]}}},[r("option",[e._v("en")]),r("option",[e._v("es")])])]),r("li",{staticClass:"title"},[e._v(e._s(e.questions[e.locale][0].title))])])]),r("div",{attrs:{id:"app"}},[r("router-view",[r("Quiz")],1)],1)])},o=[function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,r=e._self._c||t;return r("li",[r("label",{attrs:{for:"locale"}},[e._v("locale")])])}],i=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,r=e._self._c||t;return r("div",{staticClass:"card"},e._l(e.questions[e.currLocale],(function(t){return r("div",{key:t.quizzes[0].id},e._l(t.quizzes,(function(s){return r("div",{key:s.id},[e.route==s.id?r("div",[r("div",[e.complete?r("h3",{staticClass:"message complete"},[e._v(e._s(t.complete))]):r("div",[e.error?r("h3",{staticClass:"error"},[e._v(e._s(t.error))]):e._e()]),r("h1",[e._v(e._s(s.title))]),r("h2",[e._v(" "+e._s(s.quiz[e.currentQuestion].questionText)+" ")]),r("div",e._l(s.quiz[e.currentQuestion].answerOptions,(function(t,s){return r("button",{key:s,staticClass:"btn ans-btn",on:{click:function(r){return e.handleAnswerClick(t.isCorrect)}}},[e._v(" "+e._s(t.answerText)+" ")])})),0)])]):e._e()])})),0)})),0)},a=[],l=r("7402"),c=r("bcdb"),u=r("221e"),w=r("6dc0"),x=r("dea5"),T=r("9134"),f=r("dd05"),p=r("92d3"),d=r("c604"),C=r("e8e3"),g=r("c7e7"),m=r("ab6d"),h=r("e873"),q=r("73f6"),_=r("5e03"),y=r("ffe3"),z=r("804f"),b=r("229a"),O=r("dbfb"),v=r("c4e5"),N=r("0050"),k=r("51b3"),A=r("dc72"),Q=r("fa5f");const P={0:l[0],1:c[0],2:u[0],3:w[0],4:x[0],5:T[0],6:f[0],7:p[0],8:d[0],9:C[0],10:g[0],11:m[0],12:h[0],13:q[0],14:_[0],15:y[0],16:z[0],17:b[0],18:O[0],19:v[0],20:N[0],21:k[0],22:A[0],23:Q[0]};var S=P,I=r("4757");const B={0:I[0]};var R=B;const W={en:S,es:R};var E=W,F={name:"Quiz",data(){return{currentQuestion:0,complete:!1,error:!1,route:"",locale:""}},computed:{questions(){return E},currLocale(){return this.$root.$i18n.locale}},i18n:{messages:E},methods:{handleAnswerClick(e){this.error=!1;let t=this.currentQuestion+1;e?t<3?this.currentQuestion=t:this.complete=!0:this.error=!0}},created(){this.route=this.$route.params.id,this.$route.query.loc?this.locale=this.$route.query.loc:this.locale="en"}},G=F,J=r("2877"),j=Object(J["a"])(G,i,a,!1,null,null,null),$=j.exports,L={name:"App",computed:{questions(){return E}},i18n:{messages:E},components:{Quiz:$},data(){return{locale:""}},watch:{locale(e){this.$root.$i18n.locale=e}},created(){this.route=this.$route.params.id,this.$route.query.loc?this.locale=this.$route.query.loc:this.locale="en"}},M=L,D=(r("034f"),Object(J["a"])(M,n,o,!1,null,null,null)),V=D.exports,K=r("8c4f"),H=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,r=e._self._c||t;return r("div",e._l(e.questions[e.currLocale],(function(t){return r("div",{key:t.id},e._l(t.quizzes,(function(t){return r("router-link",{key:t.id,staticClass:"link",attrs:{to:"quiz/"+t.id}},[e._v(" "+e._s(t.title)+" ")])})),1)})),0)},U=[],Z={name:"Home",data(){return{locale:""}},computed:{questions(){return E},currLocale(){return this.$root.$i18n.locale}},i18n:{messages:E},watch:{locale(e){this.$root.$i18n.locale=e}},created(){this.route=this.$route.params.id,this.$route.query.loc?this.locale=this.$route.query.loc:this.locale="en"}},X=Z,Y=Object(J["a"])(X,H,U,!1,null,null,null),ee=Y.exports,te=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement;e._self._c;return e._m(0)},re=[function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,r=e._self._c||t;return r("div",[r("p",[e._v("Sorry, wrong number!")])])}],se={},ne=Object(J["a"])(se,te,re,!1,null,null,null),oe=ne.exports;s["a"].use(K["a"]);const ie=new K["a"]({mode:"history",base:"/",routes:[{path:"/",name:"home",component:ee},{path:"/quiz/:id",name:"Quiz",component:$},{path:"/:pathMatch(.*)*",name:"NotFound",component:oe,meta:{title:"Not Found"}}]});ie.beforeEach((e,t,r)=>{r()});var ae=ie,le=r("a925");s["a"].config.productionTip=!1,s["a"].use(le["a"]);const ce=new le["a"]({locale:"en",fallbackLocale:"en"});new s["a"]({i18n:ce,router:ae,render:e=>e(V)}).$mount("#app")},"5e03":function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":115,"title":"Language Modeling: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Which of the following can be considered a language model?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Word2Vec embeddings","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Embedding layer in RNN","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"RNN used for text classification","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"A language model should be able to ____ the next word in the sentence","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"use","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"predict","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"guess","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Language models are trained on","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"language vocabulary","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"specially labeled data","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"any natural text","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"id":215,"title":"Language Modeling: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Which of the architectures predicts a word from neighboring words?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"CBoW","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Skip-gram","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"N-Gram","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"When we train a CBoW model, we obtain","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"A model that can generate text","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Word2Vec embedding vectors","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Text classification model","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"The CBoW model is based on","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Dense neural network","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Convolutional neural network","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Recurrent neural network","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},"6dc0":function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":104,"title":"Neural Networks: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"The quality of prediction is measured by Loss function","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"One layer network is capable of classifying ____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"linearly joined classes","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"linearly separable classes","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"single layers of classes","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"The method of training multi-layered perceptron is called ____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"back propagation","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"multiple propagation","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"front propagation","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":204,"title":"Neural Networks: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"We use ____ for regression loss functions","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"absolute error","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"mean squared error","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"all of the above","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"All but one is a type of classification loss function","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"0-1 loss","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"binary loss","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"logistic loss","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Cross-entropy loss is a function that can calculate similarity between two arbitrary probability distributions","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},"73f6":function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":114,"title":"Embeddings: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Embedding is used to represent words with _____ dimensional dense vectors","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"lower","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"higher","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"average","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Word2Vec pre-trained embeddings can also be used in place of embedding layer in neural networks","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Using embedding layer we cannot switch from bag-of-words to embedding bag","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"id":214,"title":"Embeddings: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Word2Vec has _____ main architectures","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Word sense disambiguation is a limitation of traditional pretrained embedding representations","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"An embedding layer takes _____ as input","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"word","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"symbol","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"number","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},7402:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":101,"title":"Introduction to AI: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"A famous 19th century proto-computer engineer was","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Charles Barkley","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Charles Babbage","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Charles Darwin","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Weak AI is a system designed to solve many tasks","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Chat bots are an example of truly intelligent systems","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"false, they are usually designed by a series of rules.","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"true, they are usually considered to be \'intelligent","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"false, but they are increasingly able to pass Turing tests as they become more sophisticated.","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"id":201,"title":"Introduction to AI: Post-Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"A top-down approach to AI is a model of reasoning called","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"strategic reasoning","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"symbolic reasoning","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"synergistic reasoning","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"A bottom-up approach to AI is based on neural networks","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"The AI Winter occurred in this era","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"1950s","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1960s","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1970s","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}]')},"804f":function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":117,"title":"Generative networks: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"RNNs can be for generative tasks","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"yes","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"no","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"_____ is a traditional neural network with one input and one output","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"one-to-one","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"sequence-to-sequence","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"one-to-many","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"RNN generates texts by generating next output token for each input token","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":217,"title":"Generative networks: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Output encoder converts hidden state into _____ output","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"one-hot-encoded","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"sequence","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"number","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Selecting the character with higher probabilities always gives a meaningful text.","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"maybe","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Many-to-many can also be referred to as _____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"one-to-one","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"sequence-to-sequence","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"one-to-many","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},"85ec":function(e,t,r){},9134:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":106,"title":"Introduction to Computer Vision: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Computer vision aims to allow computers gain understanding of _____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"images","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"text","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"computers","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Python libraries available for image processing includes","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"OpenCV","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Pillow","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"a and b","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Images cannot be represented as NumPy arrays in Python","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"id":206,"title":"Introduction to Computer Vision: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Optical Flow helps us to understand how each pixel on video frames move.","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"_____ computes the vector field that shows where each pixel is moving","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Sparse Optical Flow","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Dense Optical Flow","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"none","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Resizing and Blurring are steps that can be taken during?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"pre-processing","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"training","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"image transformation","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},"92d3":function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":108,"title":"Pre-trained Networks and Transfer Learning: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Transfer learning approach uses untrained models for classification","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"One of these is not a normalization technique?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"height normalization","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"weight normalization","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"layer normalization","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"We choose Stochastic Gradient Descent(SGD) in deep learning because classical gradient descent can be ____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"fast","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"slow","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"id":208,"title":"Pre-trained Networks and Transfer Learning: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Dropout layers act as a ____ technique","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"gradient boosting","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"training","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"regularization","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"freezing weights of convolutional feature extractor can be done by ____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"setting `requires_grad` property to `False`","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"setting `trainable` property to `False`","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"a and b","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Batch normalization is to bring values that flow through the ____ to right interval","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"algorithms","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"batches","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"neural network","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}]')},ab6d:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":112,"title":"Segmentation: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"How many segmentation algorithm are there?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Segmentation is a _____ task","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"computer vision","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"natural language processing","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"neural networks","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Segmentation networks consist of ____ and ____ parts","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"classifier, divider","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"encoder, decoder","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"generator, discriminator","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":212,"title":"Segmentation: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"____ extracts features from an input image","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"decoder","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"generator","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"encoder","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"____ transforms input features into mask image","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"decoder","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"generator","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"encoder","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"SegNet relies on ____ to train multi-layered network","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"batch normalization","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"height normalization","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"weight normalization","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},bcdb:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":102,"title":"Knowledge Representation and Expert Systems: Pre-Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"The top-down approach to creating intelligent systems was based on:","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"knowledge seeking and reading","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"knowledge representation and reasoning","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"knowledge reasoning and seeking","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Knowledge is the same as information","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Knowledge is obtained by an:","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"active learning process","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"passive learning process","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"both of these","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":202,"title":"Knowledge Representation and Expert Systems: Post-Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"The simplest method of knowledge representation is:","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"algorithmic","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"symbolic","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"synergistic","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Scenarios can represent complex situations that can unfold in time","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Forward inference starts with initial data and then:","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"executes a reasoning loop","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"looks for a goal","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"starts over","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},c4e5:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":120,"title":"Language Models: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"What does GPT stand for?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Generic Pre-Trained network","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Generative Pre-trained Transformers","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Generic Positional Text","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What can GPT be used for?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Text generation","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Text classification","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Both text generation and other tasks","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"GPT is based on transformer architecture","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":220,"title":"Language Models: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"What is zero-shot learning?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Getting an answer from pre-trained network","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Training the network from scratch","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Training the network only for one epoch","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Prompt engineering can be used with","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Zero-shot learning","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Few-shot learning","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Both","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Which metric can be used to estimate the quality of a language model?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"accuracy","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"recall","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"perplexity","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}]')},c604:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":109,"title":"Autoencoders: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Self-supervised learning uses ____ data for training","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"pre-trained","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"raw","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"labeled","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Encoder Network coverts input images into latent spaces","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"VAE is short for?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Variable AutoEncoding","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Variation auto-encoder","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Variational automated encoders","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":209,"title":"Autoencoders: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Properties of autoencoders include","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"it is data Specific","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"works on unlabeled data","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"all of the above","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Auto encoders can be used to effectively remove noise from images","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Variational auto-encoders loss function does not consist of which of these?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"reconstruction loss","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"KL loss","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"TF loss","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}]')},c7e7:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":111,"title":"Object Detection: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Neural networks can only be used to classify images","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"With object detection, we don\'t just get the class of an object, but also its ____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"shape","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"location","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"type","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many objects can an object detection model detect?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"one","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"two","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"any number","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"id":211,"title":"Object Detection: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"An Object detection model gives us","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"object class","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"bounding box","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"both class and bounding box","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Which object detection models are faster?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"one-pass models","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"region proposal networks","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Fast R-CNN","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which metric can be used to determine how well bounding boxes are aligned?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"accuracy","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"precision","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"IoU","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}]')},dbfb:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":119,"title":"Named Entity Recognition: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"What does NER stands for?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Nearest Estimated Region","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Nearest Entity Region","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Named Entity Recognition","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"An entity always consists of one token","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"To train NER model, we need","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Labeled dataset","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Any natural text","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Translated texts in two languages","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":219,"title":"Named Entity Recognition: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"NER model is essentially a ____ model","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"text classification","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"token classification","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"text regression","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which neural network types can be used for NER?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"RNNs","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Transformers","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Both RNNs and Transformers","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"NER model is a good example of ____ network architecture","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"one-to-one","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"one-to-many","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"many-to-many","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}]')},dc72:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":123,"title":"Multi-Agent Modeling: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"By modeling the behavior of simple agents, we can understand more complex behaviors of a system.","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"The principle of metasystem transition is derived from:","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Evolutionary Cybernetics","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Emergentism","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"both of these","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Multi-Agent systems emerged in the ____:","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"1970s","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1980s","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1990s","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"id":223,"title":"Multi-Agent Modeling: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"An agent is:","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"an entity that lives alone","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"an entity that lives in an environment","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"an entity that is intelligent","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Reactive agents usually have:","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"simple request-response behavior","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"complex behavior","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"no behavior","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Multi-agent systems are used in:","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"video production and systems modeling","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"games and automations","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"both the above","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}]')},dd05:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":107,"title":"Convolutional Neural Networks: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"To extract patterns from images we use?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"convolutional filters","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"extractor","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"filters","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"One of these is not a CNN Architecture","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"ResNet","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"MobileNet","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"TensorFlow","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"CNN are mostly used for computer vision tasks.","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":207,"title":"Convolutional Neural Networks: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Which pooling layer is used \\"scale down\\" the size of the image","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"average pooling","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"max pooling","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"a and b","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Convolutional networks generalizes much better","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"To train our neural network, we need to convert images to tensors","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},dea5:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":105,"title":"Frameworks: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Deep Neural Network training requires a lot of computations","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Overfitting occurs because of ____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Not enough testing data","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Too powerful model","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Too much noise in output data","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Bias errors are caused by our ____ not being able to capture the relationship between training data correctly.","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"model","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"algorithm","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"computer","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":205,"title":"Frameworks: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"After compiling our model object, we train by calling ____ function","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"fit","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"train","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"teach","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Binary cross-entropy is also called log loss","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"TensorFlow is to ____ while PyTorch is to ____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Facebook, Google","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Google, Facebook","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Microsoft, Google","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},e873:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":113,"title":"Text Representation: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Each word in a Bag of Words is linked to a vector index","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Text can be represented using _____ approaches","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Character level representation represents each _____ as a number","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"letter","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"word","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"symbol","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":213,"title":"Text Representation: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Word level representation represents _____ as a number","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"letter","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"word","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"symbol","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"N-Grams refers to _____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"combination of n number of words and symbols","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"combination of n number of letters","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"combination of n number of Words","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"The main drawback of N-gram is that the vocabulary size grows fast","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},e8e3:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":110,"title":"Generative Adversarial Networks: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Generators take vectors and produce ____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"videos","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"image","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"gif","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"GANs is short for?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"General adversarial networks","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Generative advisor networks","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Generative adversarial networks","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"GAN uses ____ neural networks","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":210,"title":"Generative Adversarial Networks: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"We can use Batch normalization and BatchNorm1D to stabilize the training","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Deep Convolutional GAN uses convolutional layers for ____ and ____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"generator, discriminator","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"CNN, generator","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"training, testing","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Problems of GAN training includes","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Sensitivity to hyperparameters","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Keeping balance between generator and discriminator","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"all of the above","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}]')},fa5f:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":124,"title":"Ethical and Responsible AI: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Why we need to worry about Ethical AI?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"AI is a very powerful tool and can cause harm","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"We need to make sure AI models do not discriminate people","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Both","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Which is the example of interpretable AI?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Expert system","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Neural network","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Image classifier","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"It is not ethical to use AI in medicine","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"id":224,"title":"Ethical and Responsible AI: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"Why an AI model can discriminate?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Because it may become unfriendly","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Because datasets were not properly balanced","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Because developers programmed it in such a way","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which of the following is not a principle of Responsible AI?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Transparency","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Fairness","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Cleverness","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Accountability of an AI system means that","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"there should be a human being involved in taking decisions, who can take responsibility","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"AI system should be held responsible for its actions","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"AI system developers should be held responsible","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Model fairness is related to","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Interpretability","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Biases","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Accountability","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')},ffe3:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"title":"AI for Beginners: Quizzes","complete":"Congratulations, you completed the quiz!","error":"Sorry, try again","quizzes":[{"id":116,"title":"RNN: Pre Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"RNN is short for?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"regression neural network","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"recurrent neural network","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"re-iterative neural network","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"A simple RNN cell has two weight _____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"matrices","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"cell","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"neuron","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"vanishing gradients is a problem of _____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"RNN","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"CNN","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"KNN","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"id":216,"title":"RNN: Post Quiz","quiz":[{"questionText":"_____ takes some information from the input and hidden vector, and inserts it into state","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"forget gate","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"output gate","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"input gate","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Bidirectional RNNs runs recurrent computation in _____","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"both directions","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"north-west direction","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"left-right direction","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"All RNN Cells have the same shareable weights","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}]')}});
//# sourceMappingURL=app.dfcb35f3.js.map